globalsportsjobs.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy

 GLOBAL SPORTS JOBS LIMITED PRIVACY POLICY

The privacy of the users (“you” and “your”) of the following URL  **[www.globalsportsjobs.com](http://www.globalsportsjobs.com/) **(collectively the  **"Web Site"** ), is important to Global Sports Jobs Limited (“ **we** ”, “ **us** ”, “ **our** ” or “ **Global Sports Jobs Limited** ”).

This Privacy Policy is designed to provide you with clear information about what personal information we collect when you use the Web Site and how we use it.

**1\. ONLINE PRIVACY PRACTICES**

1.1 We are keen to strike a fair balance between your personal privacy and ensuring you obtain full value from the Web Site and other products and services we may be able to market to you.

1.2 We respect your right to privacy and we understand that, as a visitor to this Web Site you prefer to control your own personal information and preferences.  For this reason, we ask you to register or to provide personal information and preferences when you visit certain areas of the Web Site or request information.

1.3 We are registered as a data controller under the Data Protection Act 1998 (“Act”) and ensure we comply with all protection the Act affords to you. For further information on the Act please visit [ **www.dataprotection.gov.uk**](http://www.dataprotection.gov.uk/). If you wish to know more about your rights please visit the Information Commissioner's Web Site at [ **www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk**](http://www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk/).

**2\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW DO WE USE IT?**

2.1 In some areas of the Web Site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit or reply to you after your visit. This would include where you first register on our Web Site or when we ask you to provide feedback to us through a contact form or when you complete any online survey.

2.2 When you do so, we may ask you to give us your name, email address, curriculum vitae and other personal information that will be needed to supply the services which are available through the Web Site (“Services”) to you. You can 'unsubscribe' at any time from the Web Site.

2.3 We use the personal information we collect from you to provide you with Services which are tailored to your requirements. We may also use your personal information:

·         to contact you regarding the products and Services that you have requested;

·         to carry out auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and enhance the Services we provide;

·         to transfer your details (including account details) to relevant third parties, public bodies, industry organisations and regulators as reasonably required for the operation of our business; 

·         to disclose your details to government and associated organisations where we are required to do so by law.

2.4 Where you have signalled your agreement during the registration process, we may also use your personal data for future email mailings, newsletters, support, notification of new products or new versions, general correspondence regarding the Services, correspondence which may relate to you and to pass the personal information to carefully selected third parties for marketing purposes.

2.5 If you would rather not receive future marketing emails from us or would not like us to pass on your personal information to third parties please inform us by sending an e-mail to [ **support@globalsportsjobs.com**](mailto:support@globalsportsjobs.com). Other than for these purposes the personal information you provide will be kept confidential.

2.6 Once you have registered with the Web Site, if you choose to make your curriculum vitae and/or other personal information visible to Recruiters (as defined in the Web Site Terms of Use), you acknowledge that those Recruiters will have access to your curriculum vitae and/or other personal information and you agree to the disclosure and processing of such information for the purposes of providing you with this Service.

2.7 Please note that as part of the Services it will be necessary for our web server to receive the personal information Job seekers send to us and to automatically pass it on to Recruiters and vice versa and this may involve the passing or access of your personal information to countries outside of the United Kingdom whose privacy practices may not be subject to the same secure standards as in the United Kingdom. By accepting the Terms of Use and this privacy policy you will be expressly agreeing to the transfer of your personal data overseas.   ** **

2.8 Unfortunately, the internet is not a secure medium and we cannot guarantee the security of data transmitted to our Web Site. However, to prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place procedures to protect the information we collect online. All of our employees are subject to obligations of confidentiality regarding information which they have access to in the course of their employment including your personal information.

**3\. USER GENERATED CONTENT**

3.1 Global Sports Jobs Limited may provide you with the ability to contribute to the Web Site by creating personal web pages (for example in your profile) featuring information about you and/or uploading your own user generated content, such as photos, notes, updates, comments, blogs, forum postings, music and videos (together, “UGC”). You may choose to give other users of the Web Site access to your personal webpage and/or share your UGC with other users of the Web Site. Global Sports Jobs Limited collects and stores UGC that users upload so that Global Sports Jobs Limited can provide you with the services you have requested. Global Sports Jobs Limited also keeps copies of UGC so that, for examples, you can review messages you have sent and other postings that you have previously submitted. Global Sports Jobs Limited also retains copies of UGC as part of the normal back-up and archiving procedures we operate to guard against data loss due to, for example, a server malfunction.

In accordance with the Web Site’s Terms of Use you are entirely responsible for any UGC that you upload to the Web Site. You also acknowledge that we cannot control, and are not responsible for, the actions of other users of the Web Site whom you may choose to give access to your personal web pages and/or with whom you may choose to share UGC. Also, although Global Sports Jobs Limited takes reasonable measures to prevent unauthorised users obtaining access to other users’ personal web pages, no such measures can be viewed as perfect and as such Global Sports Jobs Limited cannot and does not guarantee that UGC which has been uploaded by you will not be viewed by unauthorised persons. Therefore, please carefully consider which UGC you intend to upload before doing so.

**4.COOKIES**

4.1 We do use cookies (defined below) for collecting user information from the site in connection with the Job seeker application process and for administrative control and we will not collect any information about you except that required for system administration of the Web server and otherwise as described above.

4.2 “Cookies” are messages given to a web browser by a web server. The message is then stored by the browser in a text file called “cookie.txt”. Each time the browser requests a page from the server, this message is sent back. A cookie's main objective is to identify users and personalise their visit by customising web pages for them, for example by welcoming them by name next time they visit the same site. A site using cookies will usually invite you to provide personal information such as your name, e-mail address and interests.

4.3 Non-registered users of the site are sent anonymous cookies to keep track of their browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile. 

4.4 Whilst you do not need to allow your browser to accept cookies in order to browse much of the Web Site, you must have cookies enabled if you wish to receive the Services or access any areas reserved for registered users.

4.5 Most browsers allow you to turn off the cookie function. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser.

You can find out more about the way cookies work at [ **www.allaboutcookies.org.**](http://www.cookiecentral.com/)

**5\. LINKS**

5.1 ** ** The terms of this Privacy Policy only apply to the personal information which we may collect through your use of the Web Site. The Web Site may contain links to other web sites which are not controlled by us. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of any such third party web sites and are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you may provide while visiting such Web Sites.

We recommend that you exercise caution and read the privacy policy applicable to the web site(s) in question.

**6.  Requesting, Removing and Correcting Personal Information**

Under the Data Protection Act 1998, you may request details of personal information that we hold about you. An official fee will be payable. If you want to make a request you should write to our Data Protection Compliance Officer at the address below.

If you believe that any information that we hold about you is incorrect or incomplete, you should write to the Data Protection Compliance Officer at the address below. Any information which is found to be incorrect will be corrected or removed as soon as possible.

Email:

Post:

FAO: The Data Protection Compliance Officer

Global Sports Jobs Limited

Staple House, Suite 1, Eleanor's Cross, Dunstable, Beds LU6 1SU

**7\. FURTHER INFORMATION**

7.1 Use of this Web Site is subject to our Terms of Use, The Terms and Conditions below and our Rules and payment procedure pages:

Global Sports Jobs Limited [ **Terms and Conditions**](http://www.globalsportsjobs.com/terms)

Additional [ **Terms for Job Seekers**](http://www.globalsportsjobs.com/terms)

Additional [ **Terms for Recruiters**](http://www.globalsportsjobs.com/terms)

7.2 If we sell the whole or part of our business which relates to the operation of the Web Site, the personal information which we have collected about you may be transferred to the new owner so that you can continue to receive the Services. If this happens we will try to ensure that any new owner protects your personal information in the same way that we do.

7.3 We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy without prior notice to you.  If you regularly use the Web Site you should continue to check this Privacy Policy for updates and amendments. You will be deemed to have accepted variations to the Privacy Policy if you continue to use the Web Site after any changes have been posted.

Global Sports Jobs Limited is a company registered in England under number: 7314821 and whose registered office is at Staple House, Suite 1, Eleanor’s Cross, Dunstable, Beds LU6 1SU, United Kingdom.

September 2010
